ELVIS MAINA

P. O. Box 43844-00100 NAIROBI www.linkedin.com/in/elvis-maina-8b3830276

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm an organized and detail-oriented Financial analyst and accountant in accordance with the GAAP expertise and experience in the full spectrum of public accounting and Finance. Collaborative team player with ownership mentality and a track record of delivering the highest quality strategic solutions to resolve challenges, propel business growth.

EDUCATION

TO DATE

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE, FINANCE, KENYATTA UNIVERSITY

- Distinguished member of university's Finance Society-Kenyatta University and Accounting Student Association
- Relevant Coursework: Advanced Financial Accounting and Reporting, Accounting Systems, Income Tax
- Cum GPA: 73.10

JAN 2018-APRIL 2022 KENYA CERTIFICATE OF SECONDARY EDUCATION, EDINBURGH SCHOOLS, MURANG'A

• GRADE: B+, 71 POINTS

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2023-AUG 2023 VOLUNTEERED AS A FINANCE ATTACHEE ST. GEORGES GROUP OF SCHOOLS, NAKURU

Working in a mid-sized public accounting firm to provide professional accounting services for individuals and business clients. Provide full range of services, include income tax preparation, audit support, preparation of financial statements, pro forma budgeting, general ledger accounting and bank reconciliation.

APRIL 2023 - APRIL 2023

BOOKKEEPER

KENJOY WHOLESALE AND RETAILERS, NAKURU

Inhouse bookkeeper for a KENJOY WHOLESALE AND RETAILERS. Maintained financial books, tracked expenses, prepared and submitted invoices, oversaw payroll.

SKILLS

- QuickBooks and Sage 50 Accounts Certified
- Statistical Packages Certified I.e. Advanced Excel and SPSS Software
- Microsoft Office Packages I.e. Access, Excel, Word and Publisher
- Money skills
- Interpersonal Skills
- Blockchain

- Gig Economy
- Digital Literacy
- Computational Thinking
- A Leader
- Exceptional oral and written communication
- Fluent in English

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

- Badminton
- Environmental conservation
- Travel

REFEREES

References will be Provided upon request.

DECLARATION

I hereby recommend myself as a good and capable person to work under your organization as an attaché in accordance with my proficiency as portrayed above.